[Music]
I guess I rolled over I've grown up in a
mostly sober childhoods over and so's my
hope foreclosure Taylor Swift don't ever
get to hold her adulthood is a pail of
that it's your job to deal with
it'll have you one get a nice quick try
and say you're excited but don't just
think it feel it
can you still when the years slip why
not cuz you're all grown up but when you
ask well out of that it's cuz you're all
grown up
bunch of fascists mash and the pleasure
centers of animals with a universal
human right to be happy
hold on to your right to feel crappy
straight-talking jaywalk I move through
the streets like a New York up the block
at the blocks it's Chewbacca with a huge
it's all cool except it's not true
breakthroughs grab soma and take to bed
home and it feels like was common in
most of our brave new world is fake news
you